# **ADAM KHOO**

### **Full-stack Developer**

@ dreamdeveloper482@gmail.com

Waterloo, ON, Canada



# **SUMMARY**

I am a full-stack software engineer with more than 7 years of hands-on experience in front- and back-end development. Always looking for challenging learning opportunities, I explored the blockchain space and wrote a fast and efficient recommender system still serving end users today.

# **EXPERIENCE**

#### Partner and Technical Lead

#### Regularswitch

- **=** 06/2020 06/2023
- · Budgeted, developed, and launched multiple web projects.
- · Mentored and managed multiple junior and intern developers
- Developed a RESTful API for the system to be consumed by iPad applications.

# Senior Full Stack Developer

#### Saint Elmo's

**=** 04/2018 - 05/2020

- · Developed web and mobile applications for this platform.
- Created a tool to publish videos to multiple platforms simultaneously using their APIs
- Designed and implemented an internal recurring task scheduler and tracker (front end and back end).
- Contributed to developing multiple websites for some top German companies.
- Maintained some internal projects.
- Integrated third-party APIs like Google Analytics, Slack, and Twilio.

### Full-stack Developer

#### **Trafik**

**=** 02/2017 - 03/2018

- Developed a permanent online and offline interactive art installation displayed on an LED wall and controlled online by users via a website.
- Analyzed requirements and prepared an end-to-end sheet of test cases for data-driven testing.
- Performed UI testing, unit testing, black box testing, white box testing, and regression testing on various applications.
- Pushed code repository updates to GitHub for code reviews at the end of each coding session.
- · Created multiple websites for local companies and artists.

# **EDUCATION**

### Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

**Singapore University of Technology and Design (SUTD)** 

**=** 04/2013 - 10/2016

# **PROJECTS**

#### Rabbit Drop REST APIs

Designed and developed REST APIs for the Rabbit Drop eCommerce web app. These APIs were consumed by the mobile apps.

# **TECHNOLOGIES**

 Web Development
 Back-end

 Front-end
 Algorithms
 Database

 HTML
 CSS
 C#
 Azure

 ASP.NET
 API Development

 Github
 Symfony
 JavaScript

 Python

# **SKILLS**

<b>HTML</b> Native	••••
<b>JavaScript</b> Proficient	••••
CSS Native	••••
React/Next.js Proficient	••••
Vue/Nuxt.js Proficient	••••
ASP.NET Native	••••
PHP Native	••••
<b>Python</b> Proficient	••••
MSSQL Proficient	••••
MySQL Proficient	••••

# **FRAMEWORKS**

React	Laravel	Vue	CakePHP	
Symfony	Symfony Flask		Django	
ASP.NET Core				

# **PROJECTS**

# Reach 100

A simple, front-end-only, number-based puzzle game. The game doesn't rely on any frameworks and is very lightweight. The concept is not original but adapted from a game of unknown origin. I also did the game design.

# KeepTruckin Back-end APIs

Created both public and internal APIs for the KeepTruckin platform.